Call Now for a FREE Quote! [1-877-OXI-FRESH](tel:18776943737) **OR**

Zip Code  QUOTE & SCHEDULE

Enter your zip/postal code above to find carpet cleaning services in your area, get a free quote or book online!

Average 4.7 Stars Based on 306,493 Reviews

* \>
* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Thank you for visiting the Oxi Fresh Franchising Co., Inc. ("Oxi Fresh") web site ("our Web Site"). This privacy policy establishes how Oxi Fresh will handle information learned about you from your visit to our Web Site. Except where expressly indicated otherwise, the word "we" in this privacy policy shall refer to Oxi Fresh. The references to "our Web Site" in this privacy policy shall refer to "www.oxifresh.com."

If you are an existing Franchisee of ours, references to "our Web Site" shall include our Web Site's "Inner Circle" section. The Inner Circle includes the "Owner's Forum" and may include other message board services, bulletin board services, chat areas, blogs, forums, and related communication facilities designed to enable you to communicate with others in the Oxi Fresh franchise system, all of which are provided solely for the use of our Franchisees (collectively, the "Owner's Forum").

Please be assured that the privacy of our visitors is of the utmost importance to us. We collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit our Web Site unless you choose to provide that information to us. By providing personally identifiable information through our Web Site, you are consenting to the terms of this privacy policy.

### OWNERSHIP OF INFORMATION.

We are the sole owner of the information we gather on our Web Site. We will only share your personal information with third parties, if at all, in the ways described in this privacy policy, or if we are required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform with the requirements of applicable law.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE.

Automatic Collections: As with most web sites, when you visit our Web Site, we automatically collect and store the following, non-personally identifiable information:

1. The date and time of the visit
2. The type of browser and operating system used (if provided by the browser)
3. The URL of the referring page (if provided by the browser)
4. The object requested
5.  Completion status of the request
6. The originating IP address
7. Pages visited

This automatically collected information is used by us to measure the number of visitors to the different areas of our Web Site and to assist us in making our Web Site more useful to visitors. This includes analyzing these logs periodically to determine the traffic through our servers, the number of pages served, and the demand for certain areas of our Web Site and topics of interest. These logs may be preserved indefinitely by us, used at any time and in any way deemed necessary by us, and disclosed to any third party without your knowledge or consent. We do not link this automatically collected data to any personally identifiable information.

Voluntary Collections: As part of our normal business practice, we use our Web Site to facilitate communication with the general public, Oxi Fresh business customers, interested franchise candidates, and existing Franchisees. In doing so, it is often necessary to collect personal information as part of that process. For example, if you are an interested franchise candidate, we may ask that you submit a Consideration Request Form stating your name, address, telephone number, email address, your desired franchise location, financial information, and other similar personal information, so that we may quickly and accurately respond to your inquiry. If you are a potential customer seeking information about Oxi Fresh services or information about a Franchisee in a particular area, you may obtain that information by entering your zip code. You may schedule an appointment for services by providing your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and a description of the services requested. If you are a current Franchisee of ours, you will need to provide certain account information, such as a username and password, to verify your right to access the Inner Circle section of our Web Site or for other purposes. On the Inner Circle section of our Web Site, you may voluntarily submit requests, error logs, and other notifications related to the Oxi Fresh Scheduling Center and other matters, in which case we will require your contact information and details in order to respond to the issue. Further, you will be required to enter certain credit card information, such as the account name, number, expiration date, and verification code, as well as your billing and shipping addresses, for products and services you purchase through the Inner Circle section of our Web Site. All personal information submitted by you is completely voluntary. If you choose to submit any personal information to us through our Web Site by completing forms requesting personal information and pressing the "submit" or similar buttons, such information may be shared within our organization, which includes our owners, officers, directors and certain necessary employees, representatives and agents, and with third parties as discussed below. We may use this voluntarily provided information for purposes of responding to your immediate request, verifying your authority to enter certain sections of our Web Site, processing a credit card charge for purchases you make, and for future contact and communication with you. We may store any personal information that you provide to us solely through our Web Site in a secure location, until such time as you request that we delete your personal information as set forth in the "Access to Personal Information" section below or until such time as we deem such personal information no longer useful in our normal business operations. Our deletion or disposal of your personal information will be performed in a manner to insure the utmost protection of your personal information.

Sharing information with third parties: We may share any non-personally identifiable information, such as the information automatically collected when you visit our Web Site, with any third party without your knowledge or consent. Generally, we will not share any personally identifiable information that you provide to us with any individual outside of our organization and franchise system, any other entity or organization, or any governmental agency, except with your prior written consent or as required by applicable law. We expressly reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that such disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. We may disclose your personal information to Franchisees, and their owners, officers, directors and certain necessary employees, representatives and agents. In particular, if you are a potential customer requesting information about Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning® services or scheduling an appointment, we may disclose any personal information you provide to the Franchisee operating in your area. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties who we contract with to support our business. In particular, we use third parties to process Franchisee credit card information and payments, and such third parties will have access to your credit card information for that purpose. We expressly reserve the right to disclose your personal information to enforce the terms of use for our Web Site or to protect the safety and security of other users.

We may transfer your personal information to a successor entity or individual upon a merger, consolidation, or other reorganization or sale of substantially all assets of the applicable business, in which we participate.

E-mail: By sending an electronic mail message to us, for example, by sending an e-mail requesting information on becoming a Franchisee of ours, you may be sending us personally identifiable information. In these cases, we may retain the information as long as necessary to accurately respond to your request. Please be aware that e-mail is not necessarily secure from interception or misdirection. For your own protection you may want to communicate sensitive information to us using a method other than e-mail.

Testimonials and Owner's Forum Posts: Our Web Site offers customers the opportunity to submit a testimonial regarding their experience with a Franchisee and the Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning® services they have been provided (a "Testimonial"). Further, the Owner's Forum on the Inner Circle section of our Web Site allows Franchisees to post, upload, and display information (each posting of such information shall be referred to as a "Post"). We may exploit and distribute information from any Testimonial or Post that you submit, throughout the world, in any manner, in perpetuity, at our sole discretion, without any compensation to you or any other party. In particular, please be advised that we may publish any Testimonial on our Web Site and in our other advertising materials.

Any personal information you submit in a Testimonial can be read, collected, or used by us or other visitors of our Web Site, and could be used for any purpose. Further, any information in a Post you submit can be read, collected, or used by us or other Franchisees accessing the Owner’s Forum. We do not ask you to disclose personal information other than your name in a Testimonial or a Post, but please be advised that your name and any other personal information you choose to provide may be used by us and other visitors to our Web Site, or Franchisees using the Inner Circle section of our Web Site, for any purpose. Those limitations and requirements for our use and disclosure of your personal information that are set forth in the other provisions of this privacy policy do not apply to information provided by you in a Testimonial or in a Post.

Text Marketing. By signing up via text, you agree to receive recurring automated promotional and personalized marketing text messages from Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning at the cell number used when signing up. Reply HELP for help and STOP to cancel. Msg frequency varies. Msg & data rates may apply.

See the terms of use for our Web Site for further terms and conditions regarding Testimonial and Post submissions.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES.

Our Web Site may contain links to web sites not controlled or operated by us, including those of other private entities and organizations. Please be aware that when you follow a link to another web site, you are then subject to the privacy policy of the new web site. We do not take responsibility for, nor make any claim or representation as to the privacy policy of any other web site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any other web site before submitting personal information to the controller or operator of such web site.

### USE OF COOKIES.

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We may use cookies on our Web Site to keep track of certain information you may enter, to enable certain features of our Web Site, to record session data regarding your visit to our Web Site, and to personalize your experience on our Web Site. We may also use cookies to maintain user session identity if you log in to any portion of our Web Site such as the Inner Circle.

We may also use cookies to determine aggregate usage data such as how many unique visitors come to our Web Site or how many unique visitors use a particular feature, to assess the technical function of our Web Site, and to generally help us gauge the effectiveness of our Web Site.

The cookies themselves will not contain any personally identifiable information, but they may be linked to any personally identifiable information that you enter on our Web Site.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change this in your browser settings. However, if you disable cookies from your browser you may not be able to access certain sections of our Web Site, including the Inner Circle.

### ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION.

If any of the personal information that you provide to us changes, or if you no longer desire for us to retain your personal information for the purposes set forth in this privacy policy, you may request the correction, update or deletion of such information by contacting us by any of the means set forth below.

### SECURITY.

The security of any personal information that you provide to us is important to us. We use generally accepted industry standards to protect any personal information submitted to us by you; however, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### TERMS OF USE.

By using our Web Site, you are bound to the terms of use for our Web Site. You can access those terms of use through our Web Site.

### CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

We expressly reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this privacy policy, such changes will be posted on this page.

### INTERNATIONAL USE.

We make no representations that this privacy policy is appropriate for locations outside of the United States, or whether access to our Web Site and the provision of information through our Web Site from such locations is permitted. Those who choose to use our Web Site and provide us with information from such other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws.

### CONTACT US.

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us in any of the following ways:

By email:  
  
[\[email protected\]](https://www.oxifresh.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

By telephone:  
  
1-877-OXIFRESH Toll Free in the U.S.

By mail:  
  
Oxi Fresh Franchising Co., Inc.  
143 Union Boulevard, Suite 825  
Lakewood, Colorado 80228  
Attention: Web Master

Carpet Cleaning Before and After Photos
---------------------------------------

What Customers Are Saying
-------------------------

### Average 4.7 stars (Out of 5)

Based on 306,493 Carpet Cleaning Services Reviews

**NJ.** - Semmes, AL - 12/11/2024

(5.0 Out of 5 stars)

I cannot say enough great things about Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning! From start to finish, the experience was absolutely seamless. The eco-friendly cleaning solution they use was a huge plus for me—it left my home smelling fresh without any harsh chemical odors. The results were outstanding. My carpets look brand new, and they dried so quickly compared to traditional cleaning methods. Stains that I thought were permanent vanished completely! Not only did they deliver exceptional quality, but the overall service was efficient and professional. If you’re looking for a reliable, eco-conscious, and highly effective carpet cleaning company, Oxi Fresh is the one to call. I’ll definitely be using their services again and recommending them to everyone I know! **RM.** - Mount Vernon, NY - 12/10/2024

(5.0 Out of 5 stars)

Carpet cleaning so fresh and clean that I almost forgot to take a shower that day! Trust me, this is a business dedicated to the giving the ultimate customer experience. **MD.** - New York, NY - 12/10/2024

(5.0 Out of 5 stars)

[### Committed to Being Green

We are The World's Greenest Carpet Cleaner®. Our eco-friendly cleaning process and products are better for your family and the environment. Click here to learn why it's important!](https://www.oxifresh.com/green-carpet-cleaning/)

[

Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning is Helping Bring Water to the World. By scheduling online, you can help Water.org bring clean water to the millions of people around the world in need.](https://www.oxifresh.com/water-org/)

### Easy Online  
Quotes

We make it easy for you. Get your free quote now!

### Save Money  
with Coupons

Checkout special deals on your area and save!

### Water Savings  
Calculator

We make it easy for you. Get your free quote now!

### Great Customer  
Service

We're standing by to help CALL  

[08/16/23 **Oxi Fresh: Celebrated by MarthaStewart.com for Red Wine…** Oxi Fresh’s Rob White Shares Expert Carpet Cleaning Tips with Prominent Publication For their recent article sharing expert tips on… Oxi Fresh’s Rob White Shares Expert Carpet Cleaning Tips with Prominent Publication For their recent article sharing expert tips on…](https://www.oxifresh.com/news/oxi-fresh-celebrated-by-marthastewart-com-for-red-wine-carpet-cleaning-expertise/)

[06/08/23 **Seize Your Boston Franchising Opportunity with Oxi Fresh’s…** Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning Unfurls Expansion Plans in Boston, Seeks Passionate Franchisees Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning, an industry leader in… Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning Unfurls Expansion Plans in Boston, Seeks Passionate Franchisees Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning, an industry leader in…](https://www.oxifresh.com/news/seize-your-boston-franchising-opportunity-with-oxi-freshs-ongoing-expansion/)

[03/15/23 **Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning: One of 2023’s Fastest-Growing…** Entrepreneur Magazine Ranks Oxi Fresh #135 Among Fastest-Growing Franchisors In Entrepreneur magazine’s recently released rankings of the fastest-growing franchise brands… Entrepreneur Magazine Ranks Oxi Fresh #135 Among Fastest-Growing Franchisors In Entrepreneur magazine’s recently released rankings of the fastest-growing franchise brands…](https://www.oxifresh.com/news/oxi-fresh-carpet-cleaning-one-of-2023s-fastest-growing-franchises/)

[03/14/23 **Oxi Fresh Franchisee Featured on Patch.com Post** Oxi Fresh’s Will Chambers Shares His Business Journey One of Oxi Fresh’s all-star franchisees, Will Chambers, was recently featured in… Oxi Fresh’s Will Chambers Shares His Business Journey One of Oxi Fresh’s all-star franchisees, Will Chambers, was recently featured in…](https://www.oxifresh.com/news/oxi-fresh-franchisee-featured-on-patch-com-post/)

[02/24/23 **Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning Appears on The Advisory…** Director of Franchise Development Matt Kline Interviewed on Top Franchising Podcast In the 50th episode of The Advisory Board Podcast… Director of Franchise Development Matt Kline Interviewed on Top Franchising Podcast In the 50th episode of The Advisory Board Podcast…](https://www.oxifresh.com/news/oxi-fresh-carpet-cleaning-appears-on-the-advisory-board-podcast-with-dave-hansen/)

[01/17/23 **Oxi Fresh Franchisee Sonia Garg Featured in Major…** Local Kirkland Carpet Cleaning Franchise Used as a Force for Good The website Patch.com, a community-oriented news platform, recently featured… Local Kirkland Carpet Cleaning Franchise Used as a Force for Good The website Patch.com, a community-oriented news platform, recently featured…](https://www.oxifresh.com/news/oxi-fresh-franchisee-sonia-garg-featured-in-major-publications/)

[12/11/24 **Professional Upholstery Cleaning: How Does it Work?** Learn the Step-by-Step Process Behind Oxi Fresh’s Expert Upholstery Cleaning Services We all have a favorite piece of furniture that… Learn the Step-by-Step Process Behind Oxi Fresh’s Expert Upholstery Cleaning Services We all have a favorite piece of furniture that…](https://www.oxifresh.com/carpet-cleaning-blog/professional-upholstery-cleaning-how-does-it-work/)

[01/11/24 **Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning’s 2023 Year in Review** A Look Back at Oxi Fresh’s 2023 Accomplishments As we look back on 2023 and look ahead to the rest… A Look Back at Oxi Fresh’s 2023 Accomplishments As we look back on 2023 and look ahead to the rest…](https://www.oxifresh.com/carpet-cleaning-blog/oxi-fresh-carpet-cleanings-2023-year-in-review/)

[10/26/23 **Combating the Global Water Crisis with Water.org** Oxi Fresh Donations Improve Access to Safe Water and Sanitation In today’s world, it may be hard for some of… Oxi Fresh Donations Improve Access to Safe Water and Sanitation In today’s world, it may be hard for some of…](https://www.oxifresh.com/carpet-cleaning-blog/combating-the-global-water-crisis-with-water-org/)

[08/16/23 **Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning Knowledge Featured on MarthaStewart.com** Oxi Fresh Expert Shares Red Wine Carpet Cleaning Tips with MarthaStewart.com! It’s the evening many dream of: candles flickering, soft,… Oxi Fresh Expert Shares Red Wine Carpet Cleaning Tips with MarthaStewart.com! It’s the evening many dream of: candles flickering, soft,…](https://www.oxifresh.com/carpet-cleaning-blog/oxi-fresh-carpet-cleaning-knowledge-featured-on-marthastewart-com/)

[06/29/23 **The Three Main Benefits of Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning** Three Special Advantages to Oxi Fresh’s Unique Approach Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning is proud to be one of the best… Three Special Advantages to Oxi Fresh’s Unique Approach Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning is proud to be one of the best…](https://www.oxifresh.com/carpet-cleaning-blog/the-three-main-benefits-of-oxi-fresh-carpet-cleaning/)

[06/08/23 **Searching for a Boston Franchising Opportunity? Become an…** Oxi Fresh Presents an Exciting Opportunity to Aspiring Boston-Based Entrepreneurs At Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning, we’re thrilled to announce our… Oxi Fresh Presents an Exciting Opportunity to Aspiring Boston-Based Entrepreneurs At Oxi Fresh Carpet Cleaning, we’re thrilled to announce our…](https://www.oxifresh.com/carpet-cleaning-blog/searching-for-a-boston-franchising-opportunity-become-an-oxi-fresh-franchisee/)

### Oxi Fresh Awards & Recognition

×

#### Unlock Exclusive Savings

##### & Specials

[\[email protected\]](https://www.oxifresh.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

GET SPECIALS

\* By completing this form you are signing up to receive out promotions and specials via emails or text message. You can unsubscribe at any time

### Own an Oxi Fresh Franchise

* Low Investment
* Home-based
* Award Winning
* Protected Territories

© 2024 Oxi Fresh Franchising CO, Inc [A Barnett Enterprises Corporation](https://www.barnettenterprises.com/)
